The hunters will be hunted.
Apex is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Edward Drake.
Ex-cop Thomas Malone is serving a life sentence for a crime he didn’t commit.
He is offered a chance at freedom if he can survive a deadly game of Apex, in which six
hunters pay for the pleasure of hunting another human on a remote island.
He accepts, and once he arrives, all hell breaks loose.
Dr. Samuel Rainsford, played by Neal McDonough.
Thomas Malone, played by Bruce Willis.
Carrion, played by Corey Large.
West, played by Alexia Fast.
Bishop, played by Nels Lennarson.
Jeza, played by Megan Peta Hill.
Apex, titled Apex Predator in the UK, is a 2021 American science fiction action film
directed by Edward John Drake and written by John Drake and Corey William Large.
It stars Neal McDonough and Bruce Willis and was released on November 12, 2021.
The film explores themes of prisoner, hologram,
decapitation, hunting, land mine.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.